govthub.com 2018-07-04

# Privacy Policy - Government Hub

The Government Hub is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the the Government Hub website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Government Hub website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

## COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Government Hub collects personally identifiable information such as your e-mail address, profile photos you upload, profile nickname, the city you live in, date of birth, gender and occupation. We do not collect physical addresses or phone numbers. The Government Hub also uses 3rd party services including Google Adsense and Google Analytics that collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. 

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the Government Hub. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by the Government Hub for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Government Hub website. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Government Hub public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: the Government Hub does not read any of your private online communications. 

The Government Hub encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the Government Hub so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The Government Hub is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Government Hub and the Government Hub family of websites. 

## USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Profile information including nickname, age, gender and photos are displayed to people in a user's personal network to support the function of the site as social community. A user's full name is used when a user invites a friend via email to join the service or attend an event, when we send notifications to a user related to their use of the service or when a user specifies in their account to make their full name public. A user's email address or other private data is never shared or displayed. 

The Government Hub collects and uses your personal information to operate the Government Hub website and deliver the services you have requested. The Government Hub also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from the Government Hub and its affiliates. The Government Hub may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

The Government Hub does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The Government Hub may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, the Government Hub may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to the Government Hub, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

The Government Hub does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as phone number, email, or address, without your explicit consent. 

The Government Hub keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within the Government Hub, in order to determine what the Government Hub services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the Government Hub to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

The Government Hub website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Government Hub or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the Government Hub; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Government Hub, or the public. 

## CORRECTING/UPDATING INFORMATION

Members can access, change and update their registration and personal information by logging onto the Government Hub and selecting the Modify Profile option. Users who leave the service may choose to have their personal information deleted by choosing an option to delete their account on the website or by contacting us. 

## CHAT ROOMS, MESSAGE BOARDS & PUBLIC FORUMS

Please be aware that whenever members voluntarily disclose personal information online - e.g., message boards, chat areas, file uploads, events, and listings - that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. By posting personal information online in public forums, members may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. 

## NEWSLETTER

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Email addresses will only be used to send the newsletter. Members may choose to opt-out of receiving the newsletter anytime. 

## USE OF COOKIES

The Government Hub website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

The Government Hub website also uses 3rd party software from reputable partners such as Google who may use cookies or other technologies to track your online behavior. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the Government Hub pages, or register with the Government Hub site or services, a cookie helps the Government Hub to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same the Government Hub website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Government Hub features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Government Hub services or websites you visit. 

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Government Hub secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Government Hub secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

## CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

The Government Hub will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Government Hub encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how the Government Hub is protecting your information. 

## CONTACT INFORMATION

The Government Hub welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that the Government Hub has not adhered to this Statement, please contact the Government Hub at /website-contactus.aspx. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
